http://www.suscotland.org.uk/cookies-privacy-terms-of-use/

Cookies
Our website uses cookies, as almost all websites do, to help provide you with the best experience we can. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone when you browse websites.
Our cookies help us:
Make our website work as you'd expect
Continuously improve our website for you
We do not use cookies to:
Store any personal data
Pass data to advertising networks
Pass personally identifiable data to third parties
Pay sales commissions
Visitor statistics cookies
We use cookies to compile visitor statistics such as how many people have visited our website, what type of technology they are using (e.g. Mac or Windows which helps to identify when our site isn't working as it should for particular devices), how long they spend on the site, what page they look at etc. This helps us to continuously improve our website. Analytics programs, like Google Analytics, also tell us how people reached this site (e.g. from a search engine) and whether they have been here before helping us to put more money into developing our services for you instead of marketing spend. The data collected by Google is set to auto-delete after 14 months.
Turning cookies off
You can usually switch cookies off by adjusting your browser settings to stop it from accepting cookies. However, doing this will be likely to limit the functionality of our website and probably a large proportion of the world's websites, as cookies are a standard part of most modern websites.
Privacy Policy
This notice describes our Privacy Policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
We aim to be clear, concise and transparent. If you have any questions, please email communications@suscotland.org.uk, or phone 0141 352 7603.
What personal information does Scripture Union Scotland collect about you/your child?
We securely store information you have provided to us, such as:
Basic personal information. This may include your name, address, email address, date of birth, etc. We use this data to contact you in line with your preferences.
Booking information for events. In addition to the above, it may include school information, dietary requirements and health information. We need this data to run our events smoothly and keep people safe.
Volunteering information. This may include details of relevant certifications you hold, availability, references and a statement of your faith. We need this data to accredit our volunteers for events and ensure they’re a good fit for their roles.
Donor information. This may include bank details, GiftAid declarations and donation history. We need this information to process donations.
This information may be collected via paper forms, or digitally, e.g. via our website, Mailchimp, or by email. We do not collect information without your permission. Data we already hold will be processed only for the purposes of legitimate interest.
We may also store some information not directly provided by you:
Cookies
PVG
Mail returns
Mailchimp
Do we share your personal information?
SU Scotland only shares information with third parties in order deliver postal communications such as @SU Magazine, or email communications like our Monthly e-News. This information is only available to these partners in order to process those communications.
Disclosure of your information
We may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is:
necessary to comply with the law, e.g. Child Protection
to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions
to protect our rights and those of our users
Links
Where there are links on our site to other sites, the content of those linked sites is not covered by this privacy policy. These other sites will have separate privacy and data collection practices. We do not have responsibility or liability for these independent policies. Links to other sites are provided by us for information only and in good faith. We are not responsible or liable for any content advertisement, product or other materials on or available from such sites.
Can I access any personal information you hold on me?
Access to your personal data is subject to GDPR. This is called a Subject Access Request. You can request access to this information at any time. You can request data is corrected, amended or removed, and can request that data is no longer processed.
You can submit a Subject Access Request by emailing communications@suscotland.org.uk. You can also submit a request by post, to:
Data Protection Officer Scripture Union Scotland 70 Milton Street GLASGOW G4 0HR
On requesting your data, we will issue a form for you to complete and return to us. Once we have received your completed form, we will respond to your request within 30 calendar days.
On what basis can you contact me and retain my data?
We are using legitimate interest as the legal basis for holding our existing supporters' details, administering donations, keeping relevant records and contacting those who have indicated their wish to receive postal mailings. Our legitimate interests include furthering our charitable objectives and providing the service our supporters reasonably expect. We also rely on explicit consent to send electronic newsletters and appeals to supporters who have indicated they are happy to receive these communications.
What options do I have?
Some information is necessary to provide services, e.g. your email address is needed if you want to receive communications by email, and health information is necessary for residential events.
Other information may be required by law, e.g. age and driving license information is required to confirm eligibility to drive at SU events.
Other information is optional, but may affect our ability to communicate with you, or affect your ability to fully participate in our ministry.
You can edit your communication preferences on our mailings page. To edit any other data we hold about you, please email communications@suscotland.org.uk, or phone 0141 332 1162.
Terms and Conditions, notices and revisions
Your use of the Scripture Union Scotland website and any dispute over privacy is subject to this policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, and application of Scottish law. If you have any concern about privacy at Scripture Union Scotland, please email communications@suscotland.org.uk and we will try to resolve it.
Our service to you evolves over time. This Policy and the Terms of Use will also change, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. The current Privacy Policy can always be found at  suscotland.org.uk/privacy.
Terms of Use
This notice describes the Terms of Use for access to Scripture Union Scotland website(s).By visiting our website(s) you are accepting the practices described in this disclaimer. If you do not accept these Terms of Use, you should not continue to use the Scripture Union Scotland website(s).
a) This website is provided by Scripture Union Scotland on an "as is" basis. We make no representations or warranties of any kind express or implied as to the operation of this site or the information content materials or products included on this site. You agree that your use of this site is at your sole risk.
b) Unless otherwise specified, the services provided on this website are for your sole personal and non-commercial use. You may not copy, distribute, modify, display, publish or sell any information, artwork, products or services obtained from the website.
c) To the full extent permissible by applicable law, Scripture Union Scotland disclaims all warranties express or implied including but not limited to implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.
d) Scripture Union Scotland does not warrant that this website its servers or e-mail sent from Scripture Union Scotland are free from viruses or other harmful components.
e) Scripture Union Scotland will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of this website including but not limited to damages for consequential loss.
f) You may not use bulletin boards, chatrooms or other interactive areas on this site for unlawful, questionable or immoral purposes.
g) These exclusions of liability will not apply to any damages arising from death or personal injury caused by the negligence of Scripture Union Scotland or any of its employees or agents.
h) All material on this website, unless otherwise credited to the relevant copyright owner with appropriate permission, is © Copyright 2004 - 2015 Scripture Union Scotland. All rights reserved.
i) These Terms of Use shall be governed by the laws of Scotland. Disputes arising here from shall be exclusively subject to the jurisdiction of the courts of Scotland.
j) Your use of the Scripture Union Scotland website(s) is subject to these Terms of Use, from the first time you access the site(s). If you do not accept these Terms of Use, you should not continue to use the Scripture Union Scotland website(s).
Alltnacriche
Annual Review
Classroom Outdoors
Gowanbank
Lendrick Muir
Serve Your Local School
Stories microsite
SU Holidays
UNCRC
Scripture Union Scotland is registered in Scotland as a charity (no.SC011222) and as a company limited by guarantee (no.SC54297). Registered office: 70 Milton Street, Glasgow, G4 0HR. Telephone: 0141 332 1162. Scripture Union Scotland is registered with the Information Commissioner's Office under registration reference ZA356097. SU Scotland subscribes to the United Nations Convention on the Rights of the Child, as reflected in UK law.
Website built by Gecko.
Copyright Scripture Union Scotland © 2020
